I am Danny.
Danny Pascal.
I'm originally from London.
And this is my wife.
This.
I'm Tunisian Pascal.
I am originally.
I'm from Guyana, South America.
And I moved to London
and then I'm in Wales now.
We spoke about moving to the country
maybe ten years ago.
Isn't it? Yeah.
It's like stepping out of London,
and I never thought I would leave.
Yeah, it was hard in this one, too.
But I was not assigned to anywhere.
I could live anywhere.
I already left Canada and,
I mean,
I guess you could say we're farmers.
We have our own business.
A farm, skin care.
We make our own
natural skin skincare products.
And we came to the farm to grow
those ingredients.
mom and dad.
Born and raised in London.
They're 67 now.
They.
They don't know this life, you know?
So then for them to pass that on through
generations
would be impossible
unless they made that that decision to.
To change their trajectory,
which, you know, they had no reason to
they had no or no desire to.
You know, they may have been small desires
like my mom getting the allotment
that was you know,
that was something that she took from
going to visit her uncle in Birmingham,
who was directly from Jamaica.
So there's an element of it.
But then there was never
let's make this practical.
And I don't mean specifically
getting into farming, just
I guess being in the country,
being surrounded by nature.
So his mum invited us
to like in one of the beds
and I was like,
Oh, this is why I was missing
hands in the soil,
because we grew so much of our own food
at home and you knew the person
who you were buying your food from,
you know, So
everything was natural as organic,
you know, buying stuff
in plastic bags that we just didn't
have that experience.
You could never catch me living in London
again, like we love where we live.
I want to smile, but I go back to
to London and I don't feel I can do that,
you know what I mean?
So and it's not something
that I would want for for our son,
especially being a black boy where you can
where you grew up.
And then all of a sudden you you feel
the need that you call hiding yourself.
We've lived across this part of Wales
for the last four years,
and it's been kind of the same experience,
you know, of of good people,
friendly people generally.
I also think of us being here
is showing people that they can do it.
And it's a like unintentional thing of us
being here
because we've come out and we're like,
Yeah, we can do it.
You know, a lot of people would think,
like with our son, because he's
the only black kid in a school
and is he going to get bullied?
Might he get called a name? Probably.
Is the same thing
more likely to happen in London
or will it as likely happen in London?
Probably.
So life away in those things
up, I'm like, yeah,
he can run on the beach,
he can climb hills,
he can run around with his sheep, he can
we can build him a friggin tree house
like he has all of these things that help
ground him as a human being.
And for me, that's more important
than focusing on the color of his skin
and then staying in a place
just so that he can see
all the people who look like him.
Because as his parents, it's our job
to instill the pride
and the cultural relevance and show him
how beautiful it is that his ancestors
made a way for him to be here
and to have that freedom
of being a human being on this planet
is something about just being able
to look instead of over the horizon
and see these rolling hills
and just see nature play out,
especially throughout the year,
you know, because when spring summer comes
and you see butterflies come out
and on this farm with foxes and badgers,
rabbits, rabbits, it's so cute.
And it's just
I mean, it's literally a Disney film.
Sometimes you can walk around here
and be like, This is crazy.
And and that's a beautiful thing.
We can literally just sit at this table
and look out that window for a day and
and be quite content.
You know, you finally get to be
the hermit. You've always wanted to be.
Exactly. Yeah.